A Guide to the Rockefeller University collection of The Medical Letter publication, 1996-2004 FA1103A
Rockefeller Archive Center
- TML, 41-63 - Cosmetic use of botulinum toxin, 1999 July 16 (Box 43, Folder 9-12)
- TML, 41-29 - Lyme disease vaccine, 1999 March 26 (Box 43, Folder 13-16)
- TML, 41-121 - Rapid diagnostic tests for influenza, 1999 December 17 (Box 43, Folder 17-18)
- TML, 41-85 - Drugs for sexually transmitted infections, 1999 September 24 (Box 43, Folder 19)
- TML, 41-85 - Drugs for sexually transmitted infections, 1999 September 24 (Box 44, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 41-33 - Depression and anxiety, 1999 April 9 (Box 44, Folder 4-13)
- TML, 41-122 - Corneal surgery for correction of refractive errors, 1999 December 17 (Box 44, Folder 14-16)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Epilepsy, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 17-18)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Epilepsy, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 1-3)
- TML - Drugs for Cardiac Arrhythmias, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 4-9)
- TML - Drugs of Choice for cancer chemotherapy, 1999 (Box 45, Folder 10-16)
- TML, 41-44 - Cilostazol for intermittent claudication, 1999 May 7 (Box 45, Folder 17-20)
- TML, 41-11 - Celecoxib for arthritis, 1999 January 29 (Box 46, Folder 1-4)
- TML, 41-61 - Drug interactions, 1999 July 2 (Box 103, Folder 1-4)
- TML, 42-51 - Ciclopirox (Penlac) nail lacquer for onychomysis, 2000 June 12 (Box 47, Folder 1-2)
  Restricted material - Open in 2026
- TML, 42-70 - Cevimeline (Evoxac) for dry mouth, 2000 August 7 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- TML, 42-13 - Sirolimus (Rapamune) for transplant rejection, 2000 February 7 (Box 47, Folder 4-6)
- TML, 42-56 - Drug interactions with St. John's Wort, 2000 June 26 (Box 47, Folder 7-9)
- TML, 42-27 - Curosurf, 2000 March 20 (Box 47, Folder 10-12)
- TML, 42-81 - Photodynamic therapy with veterfporfin (Visudyne) for macular degeneration, 2000 September 4 (Box 47, Folder 13-15)
- TML, 42-57 - Drugs for rheumatoid arthritis, 2000 July 10 (Box 47, Folder 16-20)
- TML, 42-113 - Phenylpropanolamine, 2000 December 11 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- TML, 42-94 - Zonisamide (Zonegran) for epilepsy, 2000 August 1 (Box 48, Folder 2-4)
- TML, 42-10 - Emergency Contraception - Plan B, 2000 January 24 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- TML, 42-42 - Oral contraceptives, 2000 May 15 (Box 48, Folder 6-11)
- TML, 42-17 - Phytoestrogens, 2000 February 21 (Box 48, Folder 12-14)
- TML, 42-29 - Calcium citrate vs Calcium carbonate calcium supplements, 2000 April 3 (Box 48, Folder 15-16)
- TML, 42-47 - Meloxicam (Mobic) for osteoarthritis, 2000 May 29 (Box 48, Folder 17-18)
- TML, 42-47 - Meloxicam (Mobic) for osteoarthritis, 2000 May 29 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- TML, 42-41 - Dofetilide for atrial fibrillation, 2000 May 15 (Box 49, Folder 2-4)
- TML, 40-102 - Colesevelam (Welchol) for hypercholesterolemia, 2000 October 30 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- TML, 42-108 - Docosanal cream (Abreva) for recurrent herpes labialis, 2000 November 13 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- TML, 42-106 - Temecteplase (TNKASE) for thrombolysis, 2000 November 13 (Box 49, Folder 7-10)
- TML, 42-113 - Valproate and other anticonvulsants for psychiatric disorders, 2000 December 11 (Box 49, Folder 11-14)
- TML, 42-8 - Prevention of malaria, 2000 January 24 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- TML, 42-37 - Lyme disease, 2000 May 1 (Box 49, Folder 16-18)
- TML, 42-18 - Aspirin for primary prevention of cardiovascular disease, 2000 February 21 (Box 49, Folder 19-20)
- TML, 42-73 - Drugs for pain, 2000 August 21 (Box 50, Folder 1-6)
- TML, 42-19 - Drugs for Asthma, 2000 March 6 (Box 50, Folder 7-10)
- TML, 42-49 - Androgel, 2000 June 1 (Box 50, Folder 11-13)
- TML, 42-97 - Drugs for prevention and treatment of postmenopausal osteoporosis, 2000 October 16 (Box 50, Folder 14-18)
- TML, 42-93 - Rivastigmine (Exelon) for Alzheimer's disease, 2000 October 2 (Box 50, Folder 19-20)
- TML, 42-93 - Rivastigmine (Exelon) for Alzheimer's disease, 2000 October 2 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- TML, 42-31 - Bexrotene, 2000 April 3 (Box 51, Folder 2-4)
- TML, 42-116 - Portable Defibrillators, 2000 December 11 (Box 51, Folder 5-6)
- TML, 42-111 - Drugs that may cause cognitive disorders in the elderly, 2000 November 27 (Box 51, Folder 7-10)
- TML, 42-36 - Substituting for troglitazone (Rezulin), 2000 April 17 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- TML, 42-109 - Atovaquone - Proguanil (Malarone) for malaria, 2000 November 27 (Box 51, Folder 12-15)
- TML, 42-39 - Ketotifen and Pemirlostat - New drugs for allergic conjunctivitis, 2000 May 1 (Box 51, Folder 16-17)
- TML - HAT - Systemic antifungal, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 18-19)
- TML - HAT - Systemic antifungal, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 42-96 - Eflornithine cream for facial hair reduction, 2000 October 2 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- TML, 42-67 - Gemtuzumab for relapsed acute myeloid leukemia, 2000 July 24 (Box 52, Folder 4-5)
- TML, 42-52 - Atkin's diet, 2000 June 12 (Box 52, Folder 6-8)
- TML, 42-71 - Hypnotic drugs, 2000 August 7 (Box 52, Folder 9-12)
- TML, 42-79 - Influenza update 2000-2001, 2000 September 4 (Box 52, Folder 13-14)
- TML, 42-35 - Exemestane for advanced breast cancer, 2000 April 17 (Box 52, Folder 15-17)
- TML, 42-12 - Epirubicin for adjuvant therapy in node-positive breast cancer, 2000 February 7 (Box 52, Folder 18-20)
- TML, 42-33 - Oxcarbazepine and Levetiracetam - Two new drugs for epilepsy, 2000 April 17 (Box 52, Folder 21)
- TML, 42-33 - Oxcarbazepine and Levetiracetam - Two new drugs for epilepsy, 2000 April 17 (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
- TML - HAT - Adverse Effects, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 3-4)
- TML - Perinopril - A new ACE inhibitor for hypertension, 2000 May 26 (Box 53, Folder 5-8)
- TML, 42-65 - Pantoprazole (Protonix), 2000 July 24 (Box 53, Folder 9-12)
- TML, 42-15 - Gatifloxacin and Moxifloxacin - Two new fluoroquinolones, 2000 February 21 (Box 53, Folder 13-18)
- TML, HAT - Antimicrobial Dosage, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 19)
- TML, 42-105 - Glyburide - Metformin (Glucovance) for type 2 diabetes, 2000 November 13 (Box 53, Folder 20)
- TML, 42-105 - Glyburide - Metformin (Glucovance) for type 2 diabetes, 2000 November 13 (Box 54, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 42-53 - Alosetron (Lotronex) for irritable bowel syndrome, 2000 June 26 (Box 54, Folder 3-4)
- TML, 42-25 - Conjugated pneumococcal vaccine for infants and children, 2000 March 20 (Box 54, Folder 5-7)
- TML, 42-69 - Meningococcal vaccine - College students, 2000 August 7 (Box 54, Folder 8-9)
- TML, 42-80 - A new long-acting methylphenidate, 2000 September 4 (Box 54, Folder 10-11)
- TML, 42-17 - Entacapone for Parkinson's disease, 2000 January 24 (Box 54, Folder 12-14)
- TML, 42-45 - Linezolid (Zyvox), 2000 May 29 (Box 54, Folder 15-18)
- TML, 42-1 - Drugs for HIV, 2000 January 10 (Box 54, Folder 19-21)
- TML, 42-1 - Drugs for HIV, 2000 January 10 (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
- TML - Rheumatoid Arthritis - Reprints, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 3-6)
- TML, 42-11 - Aggrenox - A combination of antiplatelet drugs for stroke prevention, 2000 February 7 (Box 55, Folder 7-8)
- TML - 42-54 - Beta Blockers for heart failure, 2000 June 26 (Box 55, Folder 9-13)
- TML, 42-83 - Drugs of Choice - Cancer chemotherapy, 2000 September 18 (Box 55, Folder 14-18)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Drugs for Tuberculosis, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 1-4)
- TML, 42-101 - Mifepristone (RU 486), 2000 October 30 (Box 56, Folder 5-8)
- TML - Osteoporosis - Reprints, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 9-12)
- TML - Asthma - Reprints, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 13-16)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Drugs for Parasitic infections, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 17-20)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Drugs for Parasitic infections, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 1-4)
- TML - HAT, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- TML - HAT, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 43-92 - Antimicrobial prophylaxis in surgery, 2001 October 29 (Box 59, Folder 1-3)
  Restricted material - Open in 2027
- TML, 43-43 - Choice of Lipid-lowering drugs, 2001 May 28 (Box 59, Folder 4-10)
- TML, 43-1 - Lopinavir - Ritonavir - A protease-inhibitor combination, 2001 January 8 (Box 59, Folder 11-13)
- TML, 43-87 - Drugs and vaccines against biological warfare, 2001 October 19 (Box 59, Folder 14-17)
- TML, 43-37 - Bivalirudin (Angiomax) for angioplasty, 2001 April 30 (Box 59, Folder 18)
- TML, 43-37 - Bivalirudin (Angiomax) for angioplasty, 2001 April 30 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- TML, 43-9 - Beta-Blockers, 2001 February 5 (Box 60, Folder 2-6)
- TML, 43-62 - Balsalazide (Colazal) for ulcerative colitis, 2001 July (Box 60, Folder 7-9)
- TML, 43-11 - Argatroban for treatment of heparin-induced thrombocytopenia, 2001 February 5 (Box 60, Folder 10-12)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Cardiac Arrhythmias, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 13-15)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Osteoporosis, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 16)
- TML, 43-69 - Choice of Antibacterial drugs, 2001 August 20 (Box 60, Folder 17-18)
- TML, 43-69 - Choice of Antibacterial drugs, 2001 August 20 (Box 61, Folder 1-3)
- TML - Antimicrobial prophylaxis and Endocarditis - Reprints, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 4-6)
- TML - AIDS - Reprints, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 7-11)
- TML, 43-91 - Post Exposure Anthrax prophylaxis, 2001 October 29 (Box 61, Folder 12-13)
- TML, 43-54 - PEG-Intron for chronic Hepatitis C, 2001 June 25 (Box 61, Folder 14-16)
- TML, 43-110 - Insulin Glargine - a new long-acting insulin, 2001 August 6 (Box 61, Folder 17-19)
- TML, 43-29 - Nateglinide for Type 2 diabetes, 2001 April 2 (Box 62, Folder 1-3)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Cancer, 2001 (Box 62, Folder 4-5)
- TML, 43-100 - Nesiritide for decompensated congestive heart failure, 2001 November 12 (Box 62, Folder 6-9)
- TML, 43-35 - Non-Sedating Antihistamines, 2001 April 30 (Box 62, Folder 10-13)
- TML, 43-17 - Drugs for hypertension, 2001 March 5 (Box 62, Folder 14-18)
- TML, 43-62 - Botulinum Toxin Type A for cervical Dystonia, 2001 July 23 (Box 62, Folder 19)
- TML, 43-62 - Botulinum Toxin Type A for cervical Dystonia, 2001 July 23 (Box 63, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 43-6 - Nebulized Budesonide for Asthma in children, 2001 January 27 (Box 63, Folder 3-7)
- TML, 42-2 - Cool Click - a needle-free device for growth hormone delivery, 2001 January 8 (Box 63, Folder 8-10)
- TML, 43-84 - Cord Blood Banks, 2001 October 1 (Box 63, Folder 11-14)
- TML, 43-59 - Initital treatment of Parkinson's disease, 2001 July 9 (Box 63, Folder 15-16)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Treatment of Parkinson's disease, 2001 (Box 63, Folder 17-20)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Treatment of Parkinson's disease, 2001 (Box 64, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 43-61 - Lung Cancer screening, 2001 July 23 (Box 64, Folder 3-5)
- TML, 43-7 - Mirena, 2001 January 22 (Box 64, Folder 6-8)
- TML, 43-109 - Darbopoetin (Aranesp) - a long acting erythropoietin, 2001 December 10 (Box 64, Folder 9-10)
- TML - Drugs for chronic heart failure, 2001 April 6 (Box 64, Folder 11-14)
- TML, 43-58 - Caspofungin (Candidas) for aspergillosis, 2001 July 9 (Box 64, Folder 15-18)
- TML, 43-55 - A new snake antivenin, 2001 June 25 (Box 64, Folder 19-20)
- TML, 43-110 - Zometa (Zoledronic Acid) for injection, 2001 December 10 (Box 65, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 43-51 - Ziprasidone (Geodon) for schizophrenia, 2001 June 11 (Box 65, Folder 4-7)
- TML, - Drugs for depression and anxiety, 2001 February 14 (Box 65, Folder 8-10)
- TML, 43-15 - PC-Spes, 2001 February 19 (Box 65, Folder 11-12)
- TML, 43-83 - Metadate (Extended-Release Methylphenidate), 2001 October 1 (Box 65, Folder 13-16)
- TML, 43-49 - Gleevec (STI-571) for chronic myeloid leukemia, 2001 June 11 (Box 65, Folder 17-18)
- TML, 43-79 - Substituting for Cerivastatin (Baycol), 2001 September 17 (Box 65, Folder 19)
- TML, 43-79 - Substituting for Cerivastatin (Baycol), 2001 September 17 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- TML, 43-89 - Insulin Aspart - a new rapid-acting insulin, 2001 October 15 (Box 66, Folder 2-3)
- TML, 43-103 - Drugs for HIV infection, 2001 November 26 (Box 66, Folder 4-7)
- TML, 43-26 - Once-a-Week Alendronate (Fosamaz), 2001 March 19 (Box 66, Folder 8)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Migraine - Reprints, 2001 (Box 66, Folder 9-10)
- TML, Drugs of Choice - Pain, 2001 (Box 66, Folder 11)
- TML, 43-25 - Direct-to-Consumer advertisements for Glucophage XR, 2001 March 19 (Box 66, Folder 12)
- TML, 43-13 - Palivizumab update, 2001 February 19 (Box 66, Folder 13-14)
- TML, 43-14 - Tinzaparin for treatment of deep vein thrombosis, 2001 February 19 (Box 66, Folder 15-17)
- TML, 43-39 - Formoterol (Foradil Aerolizer) for asthma, 2001 May 14 (Box 66, Folder 18-20)
- TML, 43-39 - Formoterol (Foradil Aerolizer) for asthma, 2001 May 14 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- TML, 43-31 - Advair "Diskus" - A combination of fluticasone and salmeterol for asthma, 2001 April 6 (Box 67, Folder 2-5)
- TML, 43-5 - Fluoxetine (Sarafem) for premenstrual dysphoric disorder, 2001 January 22 (Box 67, Folder 6-8)
- TML, 43-57 - Levothyroxine, 2001 July 9 (Box 67, Folder 9-11)
- TML, 43-28 - Detrol LA and Ditropan XL for overactive bladder, 2001 April 2 (Box 67, Folder 12-13)
- TML, 43-27 - Prozac Weekly, 2001 April 2 (Box 67, Folder 14)
- TML - Drugs for migraine, 2001 (Box 67, Folder 15-17)
- TML - Drugs for migraine, 2001 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- TML, 43-67 - Twinrix - A combination Hepatitis A and B vaccine, 2001 August 6 (Box 68, Folder 2-4)
- TML, 43-81 - Influenza prevention 2001-2002, 2001 September 17 (Box 68, Folder 5-8)
- TML, 43-33 - Topical tacrolimus treatment for atopic dermatitis, 2001 April 16 (Box 68, Folder 9-12)
- TML, 43-42 - Glucowatch Biographer - A noninvasive glucose monitoring device, 2001 May 14 (Box 68, Folder 13-14)
- TML, 43-99 - Cardiovascular Safety of COX-2 Inhibitors, 2001 November 12 (Box 68, Folder 15-17)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Hypertension and Heart Failure, 2001 (Box 68, Folder 18)
- TML, 43-23 - Over-the-Counter (OTC) Cough Remedies, 2001 March 19 (Box 68, Folder 19-21)
- TML, 43-23 - Over-the-Counter (OTC) Cough Remedies, 2001 March 19 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- TML, 43-3 - Drugs for Vulvovaginal Candidiasis, 2001 January 8 (Box 69, Folder 2-4)
- TML, 43-40 - Epoetin - Erythropoietin (Procrit; Epogen) Revisited, 2001 May 14 (Box 69, Folder 5-8)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Epilepsy, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 9-12)
- TML, 43-36 - Esomeprazole (Nexium), 2001 April 30 (Box 69, Folder 13-14)
- TML, 43-111 - Update on glucosamine for osteoarthritis, 2001 December 10 (Box 69, Folder 15-17)
- TML, 43-53 - Galantamine (Reminyl) for Alzheimer's disease, 2001 June 25 (Box 69, Folder 18-20)
- TML, 43-80 - Oxycodone and Oxycontin, 2001 September 17 (Box 70, Folder 1-4)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Asthma - Reprints, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 5-7)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Hypertension - Reprints, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 8-10)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Epilepsy - Reprints, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 11-13)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Arthritis - Reprints, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 14-15)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Depression and Anxiety, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 16-17)
- TML, 44-105 - Adefovir (Hespera) for chronic Hepatitis B infection, 2002 December 9 (Box 71, Folder 1-4)
  Restricted material - Open in 2028
- TML, 44-67 - Alosetron (Lotronex) revisited, 2002 August 5 (Box 71, Folder 5-8)
- TML, 44-1 - Prevention and treatment of injury from chemical biological warfare, 2002 January 7 (Box 71, Folder 9-11)
- TML, 44-18 - Anakinra (Kineret) for rheumatoid arthritis, 2002 February 18 (Box 71, Folder 12-13)
- TML, 44-19 - Almotriptan (Axert) and Frovatriptan (Friva) for migraine, 2002 February 18 (Box 71, Folder 14-16)
- TML, 44-110 - Hemolysis from Ceftriaxone, 2002 November 25 (Box 71, Folder 17-19)
- TML, 44-6 - Budesonide (Entocort EC) for Crohn's disease, 2002 January 21 (Box 71, Folder 20-21)
- TML, 44-109 - Dustateride (Avodart) for benign prostatic hyperplasia, 2002 December 23 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- TML, 44-55 - Yasmin - an oral contraceptive with a new progestin, 2002 June 24 (Box 72, Folder 2-7)
- TML, 44-8 - Othro Evra - A contraceptive patch, 2002 January 21 (Box 72, Folder 8-9)
- TML, 44-42 - Copyright violations, 2002 April 29 (Box 72, Folder 10)
- TML, 44-89 - Generic drugs, 2002 October 14 (Box 72, Folder 11-13)
- TML, 44-77 - Gefitinib (Iressa) for advanced non-small cell lung cancer, 2002 September 2 (Box 72, Folder 14-16)
- TML, 44-103 - GHB for nacolepsy, 2002 December 9 (Box 72, Folder 17-19)
- TML - Fungal Infections, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 20)
- TML - Fungal Infections, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- TML, 44-65 - Fulvestrant (Faslodex) for advanced breast cancer, 2002 July 22 (Box 73, Folder 2-4)
- TML, 44-5 - Cefditoren (Spectracef) - A new oral cephalosporin, 2002 January 21 (Box 73, Folder 5-7)
- TML, 44-93 - Drugs past their expiration date, 2002 October 28 (Box 73, Folder 8-10)
- TML, 44-83 - Escitalopram (Lexapro) for depression, 2002 September 30 (Box 73, Folder 11-12)
- TML, 44-43 - Fondaparinux (Arixtra) - a new anticoagulant, 2002 May 13 (Box 73, Folder 13-15)
- TML - Cefepime, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 16-18)
- TML, 44-126 - Eratapenem - a new parenteral carbapenem, 2002 March 18 (Box 73, Folder 19-21)
- TML - Echinacea, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 44-47 - Botulinum Toxin (Botox Cosmetic) for frown lines, 2002 May 27 (Box 74, Folder 4-6)
- TML - Fungal Infections - Reprints, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- TML - Drugs for Asthma - Treatment Guidelines, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 8-19)
- TML - Drugs for Asthma - Treatment Guidelines, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 44-73 - Neotame - a new artificial sweetner, 2002 August 19 (Box 75, Folder 3-4)
- TML, 44-95 - Valacyclovir (Valtrex) for herpes labialis, 2002 November 11 (Box 75, Folder 5-6)
- TML - Drugs for prevention and treatment of postmenopausal osteoporosis - Treatment Guidelines, 2002 November 1 (Box 75, Folder 7-10)
- TML, 44-9 - Drugs for Non-HIV viral infections, 2002 February 4 (Box 75, Folder 11-17)
- TML, 44-39 - Valdecoxib (Bextra) - a new COX2 inhibitor, 2002 April 29 (Box 75, Folder 18-19)
- TML, 44-39 - Valdecoxib (Bextra) - a new COX2 inhibitor, 2002 April 29 (Box 76, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 44-52 - Tazarotene (Tazorac) for acne, 2002 June 10 (Box 76, Folder 3-5)
- TML - Safety of antimicrobials in pregnancy, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 6-9)
- TML, 44-63 - Voriconazole, 2002 July 22 (Box 76, Folder 10-14)
- TML - Cardiovascular drugs in the ICU - Treatment Guidelines, 2002 December (Box 76, Folder 15-20)
- TML, 44-51 - Triptorelin Pamoate (Trelstar), 2002 June 10 (Box 77, Folder 1-4)
- TML - Drugs for Tuberculosis, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 5-8)
- TML, 44-80 - Tepostinil (Remodulin) for pulmonary arterial hypertension, 2002 September 16 (Box 77, Folder 9-11)
- TML, 44-59 - Drugs that may cause psychiatric symptoms, 2002 July 8 (Box 77, Folder 12-16)
- TML, 44-79 - Tegaserod Maleate (Zelnom) for IBS with constipation, 2002 September 16 (Box 77, Folder 17-19)
- TML - HAT, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 20)
- TML - Drugs for sexually transmitted infections, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 21)
- TML - Drugs for sexually transmitted infections, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 44-75 - Influenza prevention 2002-2003, 2002 September 2 (Box 78, Folder 4-6)
- TML, 44-33 - Advice for travelers, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 7-9)
- TML, 44-97 - Potassium Iodine for thyroid protection in a nuclear accident or attack, 2002 November 11 (Box 78, Folder 10-11)
- TML, 44-91 - Acetaminophen safety, 2002 October 28 (Box 78, Folder 12-16)
- TML, 44-57 - New treatments for actinic keratoses, 2002 June 24 (Box 78, Folder 17-19)
- TML, 44-57 - New treatments for actinic keratoses, 2002 June 24 (Box 79, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 44-21 - Acute reactions of drug abuse, 2002 March 4 (Box 79, Folder 3-6)
- TML, 44-71 - Tests for drug abuse, 2002 August 19 (Box 79, Folder 7-10)
- TML, 44-82 - Accutane, 2002 September (Box 79, Folder 11-12)
- TML, 44-50 - Spinal Manipulation, 2002 May 22 (Box 79, Folder 13-15)
- TML, 44-101 - Irbritumomab tiuxetan (Zevalin) for non-hodgkins lymphoma, 2002 November 25 (Box 79, Folder 16-17)
- TML, 44-101 - Irbritumomab tiuxetan (Zevalin) for non-hodgkins lymphoma, 2002 November 25 (Box 80, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 44-17 - Drotecogin - Activated Protein C (Xigris) for Severe Sepsis, 2002 February 18 (Box 80, Folder 3-7)
- TML, 44-78 - Hormone replacement therapy, 2002 September 2 (Box 80, Folder 8-9)
- TML, 44-30 -Bosentan (Tracleer) for pulmonary arterial hypertension, 2002 April 11 (Box 80, Folder 10-12)
- TML, 44-45 - Dexmethylphenidate (Focalin) for ADHD, 2002 May 13 (Box 80, Folder 13-14)
- TML, 44-53 - Droperidol Risk - Arrhythmias, 2002 June 10 (Box 80, Folder 15-16)
- TML, 44-84 - Herbal Products - Problems with dietary supplements, 2002 September 30 (Box 80, Folder 17-19)
- TML, 44-96 - Rasburicase, 2002 November 11 (Box 81, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 44-88 - Three beta-interferons for MS, 2002 October 14 (Box 81, Folder 3-6)
- TML, 44-99 - Indications for an implantable cardioverter defibrillator, 2002 November 25 (Box 81, Folder 7-9)
- TML - Drugs for Diabetes - Treatment Guidelines, 2002 September (Box 81, Folder 10-13)
- TML, 44-87 - Once-a-Week risedronate (Actonel), 2002 October 14 (Box 81, Folder 14-15)
- TML, 44-48 - Topical Primecrolimus (Elidel) for treatment of atopic dermatitis, 2002 May 27 (Box 81, Folder 16-17)
- TML, 44-107 - Metaglip and Avandamet for type 2 diabetes, 2002 December 23 (Box 82, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 44-27 - Desloratadine, 2002 March 18 (Box 82, Folder 4-6)
- TML, 44-41 - Pantoprazole (Protonix IV), 2002 April 29 (Box 82, Folder 7-8)
- TML, 44-69 - Olmesartan (Benicar) for hypertension, 2002 August 5 (Box 82, Folder 9-12)
- TML - Drugs for Parasitic Infections, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 13-16)
- TML, 44-44 - Pegfilgrastin (Neulasta) for prevention of febrile neutropenia, 2002 May 13 (Box 82, Folder 17-19)
- TML, 45-25 - Adalimumab (Humira) for rheumatoid arthritis, 2003 March 31 (Box 83, Folder 1-3)
  Restricted material - Open in 2029
- TML, 45-31 - Alefacept (Amevive) for treatment of psoriasis, 2003 April 14 (Box 83, Folder 4-6)
- TML, 45-43 - Alprazolam XR for panic disorder, 2003 May 26 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- TML, 45-15 - Aripiprazole (Abilify) for schizophrenia, 2003 February 17 (Box 83, Folder 8-10)
- TML, 45-5 - Augmentin XR, 2003 January 20 (Box 83, Folder 11-13)
- TML, 45-50 - Blue Light (Clearlight) for acne vulgaris, 2003 June 23 (Box 83, Folder 14-15)
- TML, 45-57 - Bortezomib for multiple myeloma, 2003 July 21 (Box 83, Folder 16-18)
- TML, 45-102 - Choice of an Antipsychotic, 2003 December 22 (Box 83, Folder 19)
- TML, 45-102 - Choice of an Antipsychotic, 2003 December 22 (Box 84, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 45-97 - Efalizumabe (Raptiva) for treatment of psoriasis, 2003 December 8 (Box 84, Folder 4-5)
- TML, 45-97 (45-333) - Eletriptan (Replax) for migraine, 2003 April 28 (Box 84, Folder 6-8)
- TML, 45-49 - Enfuvirtide (Fuzeon) for HIV infection, 2003 June 23 (Box 84, Folder 9-11)
- TML, 45-89 - Growth hormone for normal short children, 2003 November 10 (Box 84, Folder 12-14)
- TML, 45-67 - Omalizumab (Xolair) for Asthma, 2003 August 18 (Box 84, Folder 15-18)
- TML, 45-7 - Oxalipatin, 2003 January 20 (Box 84, Folder 19)
- TML, 45-7 - Oxalipatin, 2003 January 20 (Box 85, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 45-38 - Oxbutynin trandermal (Oxytrol) for overactive bladder, 2003 May 12 (Box 85, Folder 3-4)
- TML, 45-54 - Rapid tests for HIV infection, 2003 July 7 (Box 85, Folder 5-8)
- TML, 45-77 - Vardenafil (Levitra) for erectile dysfunction, 2003 September 29 (Box 85, Folder 9-12)
- TML, 45-11 - Atomoxetine (Strattera), 2003 February 3 (Box 85, Folder 13-15)
- TML, 45-15 - Buprenorphine - an alternative to methadone, 2013 February 17 (Box 85, Folder 16-20)
- TML, 45-74 - Agalsidase beta (Fabrazyme) for Fabry disease, 2003 September 15 (Box 86, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 45-39 - Eplerenone (Inspra), 2003 May 12 (Box 86, Folder 4-6)
- TML, 45-98 - New Glucose-Monitoring Devices, 2003 December 8 (Box 86, Folder 5A-6A)
- TML, 45-98 - New Glucose-Monitoring Devices, 2003 December 8 (Box 86, Folder 7-9)
- TML, 45-101 - Tadalafil (Cialis) for Erectile dysfunction, 2003 December 22 (Box 86, Folder 10-11)
- TML, 45-95 - Tattoo Removal, 2003 November 24 (Box 86, Folder 12-13)
- TML, 45-51 - Priloscec, Nexium and stereoisomers, 2003 June 23 (Box 86, Folder 14)
- TML, 45-65 - Immunization, Influenza, Flumist, 2003 August 18 (Box 86, Folder 15-16)